dubturbo.com 2012-06-23

# DUBturbo - Make Beats Online - Privacy Policy

_Privacy Policy:_

**Privacy Policy**  
This Web site is owned and controlled by DubTurbo.com . 

DubTurbo.com is committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services. Although DubTurbo.com respects the privacy of all those who visit our Site and use our online services, we do collect information from and about our users. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service, and other published guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information (as described below) about users of this Site without their permission. 

Effect of This and Related Documents: This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Service and other published guidelines, governs your interaction with this Site, and your registration for and use of DubTurbo.com 's online services. 

Periodic Policy Changes: Please note that DubTurbo.com reviews its privacy practices from time to time (e.g., to track technology and/or legal changes), and that those practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy. 

Opt-Out Option: If you would like to have your personally-identifiable information removed from DubTurbo.com 's databases going forward, please email [support@dubturbo.com](mailto:support@dubturbo.com), and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. However, there will be residual information that will remain within DubTurbo.com 's databases, access logs, and other historical internal records, which may or may not contain such personally-identifiable information. 

Your Requesting Available Information About You: If you want to find out what information DubTurbo.com has in its database about you, please email [support@dubturbo.com](mailto:support@dubturbo.com)

. Please include your name, email address, and other information in the same format that you originally supplied to DubTurbo.com , so we can be more certain of matching your request to the correct information. 

**The Information We May Gather**

_Non-personally-identifiable information_

General: When users come to our Site, we collect and aggregate information indicating their home server, but not their e-mail addresses. Such information helps us identify the most popular content and portions of our Site and determine the effectiveness of our various promotional activities. We aggregate such information for internal review and thereafter it’s superseded by more recent information. 

_Personally Identifiable Information_

(a) General: In certain areas of this Site, we require that you provide us with personally-identifiable information, in order to be able to use that portion or those portions of this Site. For instance, the names and contact information of persons who visit our Web sites are added to our data base so that, for example, they may be contacted in the future regarding DubTurbo.com ‘s products, services or future opportunities. Such contact may occur by email, telephone or mail, as DubTurbo.com deems appropriate. 

(b) Lack of DubTurbo.com Responsibility For Third Party Content On Site: DubTurbo.com cannot and does not control the acts of the users of its Web site's services or monitor the accuracy of postings by such users. All users should be aware that, when they disclose personally identifiable information in a bulletin board, chat room, or other forum or public area of this Site, the information might be collected, circulated, and used by others. In the event that you encounter any user who is improperly collecting or using information about you or other users, 

please contact us at [mailto:support@dubturbo.com](mailto:support@dubturbo.com)

_How We Use The Information We Gather_

How We Use Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We aggregate data on users' home servers for internal review purposes, in order to build higher quality, more useful online services and better products, e.g., by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users. Following such internal review, such aggregated information is then superseded by more recent information. 

How We Use Personally-Identifiable Information: DubTurbo.com provides notice to users that personally-identifiable (i.e., non-aggregated) information will be collected during the Web-browsing process; this Privacy Policy also serves as notice that such information is collected under those circumstances. DubTurbo.com may use such information to enhance your experience by providing such information to appropriate third parties, including any outsourcers, as reviewed and selected by DubTurbo.com . 

DubTurbo.com reserves the right to disclose information contained in our access logs concerning any user as we reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business. In particular, we reserve the right to disclose such when a user is in violation of our current or later Terms of Service or other published guidelines, or initiates or participates (or is reasonably believed so) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order, and to disclose such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law. 

In reviewing the information above, please keep in mind that DubTurbo.com cannot and does not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including other Site users, including the manner in which they might use information received either from DubTurbo.com or independently.
